{
    "questions":[
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is a set in Python?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "A data structure that stores elements in a sequential order.",
          "A collection of unordered and unique elements.",
          "A type of dictionary that stores key-value pairs.",
          "A container that holds only numeric values."
        ],
        "answer": "A collection of unordered and unique elements."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "How do you create an empty set in Python?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "set()",
          "{}",
          "[]",
          "()"
        ],
        "answer": "set()"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a valid set in Python?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "{1, 2, 2, 3}",
          "{1, 2, 'hello', (1, 2)}",
          "{1, 2, [3, 4]}",
          "set([1, 2, 3])"
        ],
        "answer": "{1, 2, [3, 4]}"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What operation is used to add elements to a set in Python?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "add()",
          "insert()",
          "append()",
          "update()"
        ],
        "answer": "add()"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What will be the length of the set {1, 2, 3, 4, 5}?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "4",
          "5",
          "6",
          "The length cannot be determined."
        ],
        "answer": "5"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following methods is used to remove an element from a set?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "remove()",
          "pop()",
          "discard()",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": "All of the above"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the result of the following set operation?",
        "code": "\nset1 = {1, 2, 3}\nset2 = {3, 4, 5}\nset1.union(set2)",
        "option": [
          "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5}",
          "{1, 2, 3, 4}",
          "{3}",
          "{1, 2, 4, 5}"
        ],
        "answer": "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5}"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using the intersection() method on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "To find the common elements between two sets.",
          "To merge two sets into one.",
          "To remove duplicate elements from a set.",
          "To check if two sets are disjoint."
        ],
        "answer": "To find the common elements between two sets."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for the difference operation on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "set1.difference(set2)",
          "set1 - set2",
          "set1 | set2",
          "set1 & set2"
        ],
        "answer": "set1 - set2"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following code?",
        "code": "\nset1 = {1, 2, 3}\nset2 = {3, 4, 5}\nset1.intersection(set2)",
        "option": [
          "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5}",
          "{1, 2, 3}",
          "{3}",
          "An empty set"
        ],
        "answer": "{3}"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using the symmetric_difference() method on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "To find the common elements between two sets.",
          "To merge two sets into one.",
          "To remove duplicate elements from a set.",
          "To find the elements that are unique to each set."
        ],
        "answer": "To find the elements that are unique to each set."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for the symmetric difference operation on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "set1.symmetric_difference(set2)",
          "set1 - set2",
          "set1 | set2",
          "set1 & set2"
        ],
        "answer": "set1.symmetric_difference(set2)"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following code?",
        "code": "\nset1 = {1, 2, 3}\nset2 = {3, 4, 5}\nset1.symmetric_difference(set2)",
        "option": [
          "{1, 2, 4, 5}",
          "{1, 2, 3, 4, 5}",
          "{3}",
          "An empty set"
        ],
        "answer": "{1, 2, 4, 5}"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using the isdisjoint() method on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "To find the common elements between two sets.",
          "To check if one set is a subset of another set.",
          "To check if two sets have any common elements.",
          "To compare the lengths of two sets."
        ],
        "answer": "To check if two sets have any common elements."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax for checking if two sets are disjoint?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "set1.disjoint(set2)",
          "set1 - set2",
          "set1.isdisjoint(set2)",
          "set1 & set2"
        ],
        "answer": "set1.isdisjoint(set2)"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What will be the output of the following code?",
        "code": "\nset1 = {1, 2, 3}\nset2 = {4, 5, 6}\nset1.isdisjoint(set2)",
        "option": [
          "True",
          "False",
          "None",
          "An error will occur."
        ],
        "answer": "True"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "Which of the following is true about sets in Python?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "Sets preserve the order of elements.",
          "Sets allow duplicate elements.",
          "Sets are mutable.",
          "Sets can contain lists as elements."
        ],
        "answer": "Sets can contain lists as elements."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the purpose of using the pop() method on sets?",
        "code": "",
        "option": [
          "To remove the last element from a set.",
          "To remove a random element from a set.",
          "To remove a specific element from a set.",
          "To return the length of a set."
        ],
        "answer": "To remove a random element from a set."
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
      "languageId": 2,
      "topicId": 35,
      "questions": {
        "question": "What is the output of the following code?",
        "code": "\nset1 = {1, 2, 3}\nset1.pop()",
        "option": [
          "1",
          "2",
          "3",
          "An empty set"
        ],
        "answer": "1"
      },
      "level": "beginner",
      "mark": 1,
      "time": 1
    },
    {
        "languageId": 2,
        "topicId": 35,
        "questions": {
          "question": "What is the purpose of using the clear() method on sets?",
          "code": "",
          "option": [
            "To remove all elements from the set.",
            "To check if the set is empty.",
            "To return a copy of the set.",
            "To remove a specific element from the set."
          ],
          "answer": "To remove all elements from the set."
        },
        "level": "beginner",
        "mark": 1,
        "time": 1
      }
  ]
}  